{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Wenczel",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/FC_Augsburg",
    "human_readable": "Michael Wenczel plays for FC Augsburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869159460067749,
            "question": "Is Michael Wenczel a member of FC Augsburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005265235900879,
            "question": "Who plays for FC Augsburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8049789667129517,
            "question": "What team does Michael Wenczel play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7770960330963135,
            "question": "For which club does Michael Wenczel compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730574369430542,
            "question": "Name a player who belongs to FC Augsburg."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7010444402694702,
            "question": "What team is known for having Michael Wenczel as a player?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6950131058692932,
            "question": "Is Michael Wenczel a football player?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6339690685272217,
            "question": "Who is associated with FC Augsburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5661324262619019,
            "question": "In what sport does Michael Wenczel participate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5119299292564392,
            "question": "What is the name of the football club that Michael Wenczel is associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Wenczel plays for FC Augsburg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1384_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what sport does Michael Wenczel participate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1384_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is associated with FC Augsburg?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1384_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Wenczel a football player?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1384_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1384_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Michael Wenczel, they don't state that he plays for FC Augsburg.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The files contain information about players and teams, including Michael Wenczel, and it can be inferred that he plays for FC Augsburg based on the context of the files."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention player profiles and statistics related to Michael Wenczel, indicating that he is associated with FC Augsburg. Therefore, the triple \"Michael Wenczel plays for FC Augsburg\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on FC Augsburg's history and achievements, particularly their youth development program. There is no mention of Michael Wenczel or any player by that name being associated with the club.  Furthermore,  information about Wenczel's profile suggests he might be linked to different teams and platforms like Flashscore.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}